{
    "subject": "resource/The_Whispers",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of The Whispers is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9769890904426575,
            "question": "Which US city could be considered The Whispers' hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8535027503967285,
            "question": "What country is The Whispers' hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8174687027931213,
            "question": "Which country considers The Whispers as their hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.691193699836731,
            "question": "Where is The Whispers from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6350887417793274,
            "question": "Is The Whispers a band from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49987825751304626,
            "question": "The Whispers are originally from which place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47230908274650574,
            "question": "What is the nationality of The Whispers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38834285736083984,
            "question": "In what nation did The Whispers originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3442564308643341,
            "question": "The United States is the hometown of which musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.343464732170105,
            "question": "Where did The Whispers establish their roots?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of The Whispers is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9288_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The United States is the hometown of which musical group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9288_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what nation did The Whispers originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9288_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of The Whispers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9288_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9288_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9288_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9288_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9288_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9288_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9288_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9288_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9288_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9288_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9288_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The Whispers' country of origin is mentioned as \"United States\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9288/re-ranker-msmarco/72.txt)\n* The Whispers are indeed an American group from Los Angeles, California (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9288/re-ranker-msmarco/72.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9288/re-ranker-msmarco/62.txt)\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"The Whispers is from United States\" and provide additional details about their formation in Los Angeles, California. This supports the claim that the hometown of The Whispers is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state The Whispers formed in Watts, California.  California is a state within the United States.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}